Contact

aswiner.dev@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aswin-erbb54a1240 (LinkedIn) www.biodrop.io/Aswin-ER (Portfolio)

Top Skills

vercel
Amazon EC2
docker

Certifications

Microsoft Excel - Excel from Beginner to Advanced

Aswin ER

Self-taught MERN Stack Developer

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

"My name is Aswin ER, and I am from Kerala. After completing my undergraduate studies, I joined a boot camp by a company called Brototype, wherein I have built my knowledge and skills in the MERN stack. I am a quick learner and have been engaging in self-learning for the past 12 months."

Experience

RippleMind Full Stack Developer September 2023 - Present (2 months) Bengaluru

Brototype Student Intern January 2023 - September 2023 (9 months) Kochi, Kerala, India

Education

University of Calicut

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Computer Application · (June 2019 - June 2022)

freeCodeCamp